<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>References on MM3* lab</title>
    <link>/ref/</link>
    <description>Recent content in References on MM3* lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>©2020 roesinn</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="/ref/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>/ref/markdown-syntax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/markdown-syntax/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Browser security</title>
      <link>/ref/browser-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/browser-security/</guid>
      <description>13. Browser Security Browser Security &amp;amp; Web Security Web browser: (client side) Attacks target browser security weaknesses Result in: Malware installation (keyloggers, bot-nets) Document theft from corporate network Loss of private data Web application code: (server side) Runs at web site: banks, e-merchants, blogs Written in PHP, ASP, JSP, Ruby, &amp;hellip; Many potential bugs: XSS, XSRF, SQL injection Attacks lead to stolen CC#, defaced sites. 13.1 Web Basics HTTP(S) is</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network security</title>
      <link>/ref/network-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/network-security/</guid>
      <description>11. Network Security 11.1 Intro Network security deals with secure communication over an insecure medium. Secure Communication properties Confidentiality Intergrity - message contents remain unaltered Authentication Availability Adversary types Eavesdropping attackers only listen; no inject(spoof), intercept or modify; how? use (remote) antenna Defense: encryption Man-in-the-middle attackers On-path; can listen, inject, block and change messages how? Control router/switch/link; route-hijacking Defense: encryption, signatures, MACs Off-path attackers Off-path (do not control devices on</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rich Content</title>
      <link>/ref/rich-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/rich-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hugo ships with several &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/content-management/shortcodes/#use-hugo-s-built-in-shortcodes&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Built-in Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt; for rich content, along with a &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/about/hugo-and-gdpr/&#34;target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Privacy Config&lt;/a&gt; and a set of Simple Shortcodes that enable static and no-JS versions of various social media embeds.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web security</title>
      <link>/ref/web-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/web-security/</guid>
      <description>12. Web Security 12.1 Intro Big trend =&amp;gt; Software as a Web-based service Online banking, shopping, government, bill payment, tax prep, customer relationship management, etc. Cloud computing But, Security =&amp;gt; poor Poorly written scripts with inadequate input validation Sensitive data stored in world-readable files Typical Web Application Written in a mixture of PHP, Java, JavaScript, Python, C, Go, &amp;hellip; Runs on a Web server or Application Server Interacts with back-end</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placeholder Text</title>
      <link>/ref/placeholder-text/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/placeholder-text/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de
pectora summo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Math Typesetting</title>
      <link>/ref/math-typesetting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/math-typesetting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Mathematical notation in a Hugo project can be enabled by using third party JavaScript libraries.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>/ref/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/ref/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ref/about/</guid>
      <description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 https://github.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
